谢谢你们赶过来
Thanks for coming by.
我们希望你们能帮我们
We wanted to bounce
想一些婚礼上用得上点子
some ideas off of you about the wedding ceremony.
-怎么了 你还好吗  -只是
- What's the matter? Are you okay? - It's just...
莫妮卡说了"婚礼"
Monica said, "Wedding."
我们希望你们之中有人能上台念些感性的文章
We thought one of you could read something.
好的  我想读诗也可以啦
Okay, yeah, I guess I can do that too.
也
Too?
我自己想了一个点子  来庆祝你们的婚礼
I kind of have something else planned for you guys.
-你能告诉我们是什么点子吗  -抱歉
- Do you mind telling us what it is? - Sorry.
我想把它当成高度机密
I'm kind of keeping this one on the Q.T.
不管你是指哪个  我希望会有眨眼睛
Whatever it is, I hope it involves winking.
-嘿  -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我跟《我日》子的编剧谈过
I talked to one of the DOOL writers...
-什么是《我日》  -《我们的日子》
- What is DOOL? - Days of Our Lives.
你们一定不相信
You're not gonna believe it.
我演的角色就要醒过来了
My character is coming out of his coma!
-太棒了  -乔伊
- That's wonderful. - Wow, Joey.
不只是那个  我还会有个新脑子
And not only that, I'm getting a new brain!
所以你的工作跟私生活都有了喜事
So great things are happening at work and in your personal life.
慢着  什么叫你要换个新脑子
Wait, what do you mean by you're getting a new brain?
他们要踢走剧中一个角色
They're killing off one of the characters on the show...
将她的脑子移植到我的身体里
...and her brain is being transplanted into my body.
什么  脑部移植手术
What? A brain transplant?
太荒谬了
It's ridiculous.
荒谬的是
It's ridiculous that
你三个半月都没性生活了
you haven't had sex in three and a half months.
现在是冬天  街上人太少
It's winter. There are fewer people on the street.
他们要踢走谁
Who are they killing off?
西西莉亚·梦露  她扮演杰西卡·罗卡哈德
Cecilia Monroe. She plays Jessica Lockhart.
不
No!
她真的非常擅长泼别人一脸饮料
She is so good at throwing drinks in people's faces.
我都没见她喝完过任何一杯饮料
I don't think I've ever seen her finish a beverage.
她扇人的方式  你不想试试吗  一次也好
The way she slaps people. Wouldn't you love to do that? Just once.
别
Don't do it.
她参演这部戏很久了
And she's been on the show forever.
取代她一定很难
It's gonna be really hard to fill her shoes.
解释一下
Help me out here.
当你做过脑部移植手术后
When you come out of the brain transplant...
你要变成她
...you are going to be her?
但是是用德雷克·拉莫瑞的身体
Yes, but in Drake Ramoray's body.
有什么难懂的
Why is this so hard for you to get?
你不是科学家吗
I thought you were a scientist.
瑞秋  那边那个男的
Rach, so that guy there...
直人还是基友
...straight or gay?
他太帅  肯定是基友
Oh, yeah, he's too cute to be straight.
波霸小姐会帮我们查个清楚
Knockers will help us figure it out.
直人
All right, straight.
而且一眼就看得出
And not subtle.
他忘了拿手机
He left his cell phone.
应该交给甘瑟  放在失物招领处
We could hand it to Gunther to put it in lost and found.
或者我们可以拿他电话给中国打电话
Or we could use it to call China,
看看那里的人们怎样
see how those guys are doing.
如果他打电话来找手机  我接了电话
What if he calls his own cell phone and I answer...
我们开始聊天  之后坠入爱河呢
...and we start talking and we fell in love?
会是个很棒的故事对吧
Wouldn't that be a great story?
像是数码时代的通话
Kind of like a fairy tale for the digital age.
听起来很棒  我要去拿手机
That does sound great. I'm gonna get the phone.
等一下  为什么你会成为故事的女主角
What? Wait. Why do you get the story?
我已经很久没有约会了
I don't know. I haven't been out on a date in so long.
菲比  三天前你才约过会
Phoebe, you had a date three days ago.
那不是约会
That wasn't a date.
那只是朋友聚会  顺便嘿咻
That was friends getting together and having sex.
好吧  我去拿手机
Okay. Great. I get the phone.
不行  一星期前你才跟泰格分手
No way. You just broke up with Tag a week ago.
之前我都觉得我很累  不会再爱了
Yeah, and until now, I didn't think I would love again.
-说得挺好  没用  -慢着
- Nice try. - Wait.
该如何公平决定谁拿手机呢
How do we fairly decide who gets the phone?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许我们应该
Maybe we could...
动作太慢
Aha! Too slow!
太大意轻敌
Aha! Too cocky.
我就要和他约会  你管不了我
I'm dating him. There's nothing you can do.
我管得了
Yes, there is.
你打算怎么做  杀了他吗
What are you going to do, kill him?
就像你杀了查尔斯
Like you did Charles?
我的宝贝
Oh, my baby.
卡
Cut!
你演得太好了
That was a great scene.
刚刚那一巴掌很逼真  你怎么办到的
That slap looked so real. How do you do that?
-那只是多年的经验  -快拿冰块过来给我
- Oh, just years of experience. - Can I get some ice here?!
我只是觉得你演技很棒
I just wanted to say how wonderful I think you are.
你该不会是那个濒临死亡的影迷吧
You're not the fan who's dying, are you?
我是乔伊·崔比安尼  昨天我们有对手戏
I'm Joey Tribbiani. We did a scene together yesterday.
-我就是那个昏迷的人  -那是真人
- I'm the guy in the coma. - Oh, that was a real person?
因为你离开剧组后
Anyway, I'm gonna say, since I'm getting your brain
我要移植你的脑子
when you leave the show...
我在想  你有没有演技小贴士
...I was wondering if there's any tips...
我要离开剧组
I'm leaving the show?
我不知道  怎么了  你有听到什么风声吗
I don't know. Why? Did you hear something?
谁告诉你的
Who told you that?
-一个编剧  -哪个  秃头还是高个子
- One of the writers. - Which writer? Was it bald or was it tall?
那不重要  因为那不是真的
You know, it doesn't matter, because it is not true.
好
Okay.
就算是真的
And if it were true,
你竟然敢来叫我教你
how dare you come to me and ask me for tips...
饰演我演了二十年的角色
...about a character I've played for 20 years!
梦露小姐  来了
Miss Monroe... Oh, there you go.
听着  我有个点子
Okay, look, I have an idea.
看看他的快捷联系人都有谁
Why don't we see what kind of numbers he has on his speed dial...
和他有最多共同点的人拿手机
...and then whoever has more in common with him gets the phone.
快捷联系人1号  妈妈
First name on the speed dial is "Mom."
我妈妈自杀了
Oh. I lost my mom to suicide.
不行  你不能利用那理由
No way. You can't use that
抢走帅哥和最后一个蓝莓小蛋糕
to get the cute guy and the last blueberry muffin.
我今天已经用过这个借口了  抱歉
Did I use that already today? I'm sorry.
我赢了  他的快捷联系人里有巴尼百货
Oh, I win. He's got Barneys on his speed dial.
你又不知道那是不是巴尼百货
You don't know it's Barneys the store.
说不定是他朋友家或者酒吧
That could be his friend's house or a bar...
谁会把巴尼百货存为快捷联系人
Who has Barneys the store on their speed dial?
他的新女朋友
His new girlfriend.
那是什么声音
What is that?
我想是快死掉的猫在举行游行
I think it's the Dying Cat Parade.
听起来是从对街传来的
Sounds like it's coming from across the street.
-我的天啊  -什么
- Oh, my God. - What?
还记得罗斯说他要在婚礼上给我们惊喜吗
The thing that Ross was gonna do at our wedding?
他和我一起出去玩的时候突然说
He was hanging out with me and said,
"你有一半苏格兰血统  对吧"
"You're half Scottish, right?"
不可能  不可能是罗斯
No. There is no way. It cannot be Ross.
不可思议  为什么你有苏格兰血统
Unbelievable. Why is your family Scottish?
为什么罗斯是你哥哥
Why is your family Ross?
他不能在婚礼上演奏  大家都会跑光的
He cannot play at our wedding. Everyone will leave.
你听  纯噪音啊
I mean, come on. That is just noise!
根本都不成调
It's not even a song.
等一下  如果你仔细听
Wait. If you listen very carefully...
我想它是库尔与伙伴合唱团的《庆祝》
...I think it's "Celebration" By Kool and the Gang.
你说的对  他们要将我踢出这部戏
You're right. They are writing me out of the show.
他们还没有决定什么时候  但应该很快
They don't know exactly when it's going to happen, but soon...
木已成舟
...and then that's it.
对不起  如果让我决定
I'm so sorry. If it was up to me,
我永远不会让你离开
you would never leave the show.
-谢谢你  -我是认真的
- Yeah, thanks. - I mean it.
简直不敢相信他们这么对你  还有你的影迷
I can't believe they'd do this to you. And to your fans.
他们一定伤心欲绝  他们那么爱你
They're gonna be devastated. Heartbroken. They love you so much.
你说的对
Oh, you're right.
谢谢
Thank you.
你说你叫什么名字
What's your name again?
-乔伊  -谢谢
- Joey. - Thank you.
你太贴心了
That is so sweet.
听着  之前我会来找你
Look, the only reason I came up to you before...
是因为
...is because, well...
因为要饰演你我真的很紧张
...l'm really nervous about being you.
如果你能帮我抓住
If you could help me capture
角色的神髓
the essence of the character, you know.
帮助我重现杰西卡  拜托了
Help me keep Jessica alive. Please?
好  乔伊  我会帮助你的
All right, Joey, I'll help you.
不是因为我欠这个愚蠢的剧集什么
Not because I owe it to this stupid show...
因为这是我欠杰西卡的
...but because I owe it to Jessica.
-那真的是太棒了  谢谢你  -别客气
- Oh, that's great. Thank you so much. - You're so welcome.
我一直在观摩录影带  你觉得这招如何
I've been watching some tapes. How's this?
杰西卡·罗卡哈德永远不会回来
Jessica Lockhart will never step foot in this place again!
永远
Never!
杰西卡不是英国腔啊
But Jessica doesn't have an English accent.
我还演出英国腔了
I can do an English accent?
我要把这点写在我履历表里
That baby's going on my resume.
-你好吗  -很好
- Hi. How are you? - Good.
还记得我们在咖啡店
Remember when we were in the coffeehouse...
我们决定我可以拿走那个帅哥的手机吗
...we decided I was gonna keep the cute guy's phone?
我准备把手机放在包包里
I was gonna keep it
这样一来电话我就能迅速接听
in my purse so if it rang, I could just pick it up?
你记得你摸进我包里把手机偷走了吗
Do you remember going into my purse and stealing the phone?
现在我就听不懂了
Now you lost me.
-你偷走了手机  -不  我没有
- You stole the phone. - No, I didn't.
如果我拨号过去它不会响吗
You're saying that if I called it, it wouldn't ring?
-不会  -好
- No. - Okay.
既然你要拨号了
But while you dial,
来看看我刚买的响铃皮包
let me show you the features of my new ringing handbag.
它真的有用
Oh, it does work.
-菲比  -是另外一支手机
- Phoebe. - That is a different phone.
是吗  你好  瑞秋在吗
Oh, is it? Hello. Yes, hi, is Rachel there?
她在的  稍候  找我的
Yes, she is. Just one moment, please. It's for me!
真是如山铁证啊
That is damning evidence.
我的天哪  一定是他
Oh, my God. I bet that's him.
数码童话即将开始
My digital fairy tale's about to begin.
你能别那样了吗
Would you stop doing that?
对  我就是捡到你手机的人
Hello? Yes, I'm the one who found your phone.
-菲比  你不能  -我在讲电话
- Phoebe, you can't... - I'm on a call.
对  今晚过来拿吧  就八点半吧
Yeah, you can pick it up tonight. Say, 8:30?
在我公寓
At my apartment.
莫顿街5号  14号公寓
It's 5 Morton Street, apartment 14.
或许之后
And then maybe, you know, after,
我们可以一起吃点东西之类的
we can grab a bite to eat or whatever.
好的  到时候见  再见
Okay. Okay, I'll see you then. Bye.
你知道他来的时候我会在这里吧
You do know that I will be here when he comes over.
你怎么知道他什么时候会来
How will you know what time to come over?
你刚刚说了
You just said it.
这个角色的精髓源自于她的自信
The essence of the character is rooted in her confidence.
譬如说  当洁西卡走进一个房间时
So when Jessica enters a room, for instance...
她拥有那个房间里
...she owns everything...
所有事物跟所有人
...and every person in that room.
-你试试看  -好
- You try it. - Okay.
他也没有对这个房间生气
He's not angry at the room either.
再试一次  他拥有这个房间
Try it again. He owns it. He owns the room.
这是他的  他拥有这个房间  他拥有它
It is his. He owns, owns, owns the room! He owns it!
这有点奇怪  但已经好多了
It's a little weird, but it's getting better.
我一定会想念这个女人
I'm gonna miss this woman so much.
我不知道我该怎么办
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
我演这部戏二十年了
It's been 20 years of my life.
或许这是件好事
Hey, hey. Maybe this is a good thing.
给你机会做改变
It'll give you a chance to shake things up.
扮演不一样的角色
Play different characters.
你才华横溢
You're so talented.
或许我该在几年前离开
Probably should've just left years ago
那时候很多人要我演戏
when the offers were pouring in...
但我在这里过得太舒服
...but I just got so comfy here and...
我拒绝了一些大好机会
I turned down some amazing work.
譬如说呢
Like what?
就说如果我在十五年前离开
Well, let's just say if I'd left 15 years ago...
现在墨西哥影坛会完全不一样
...the landscape of Mexican cinema would be very different today.
但现在现在时机不一样了
But, well, now... Now's a different time for me.
别自怨自艾
Oh, hey, come on. Don't do this.
我告诉你点事  好吗
Let me tell you something, okay?
当我看到你演戏时
When I watch you do a scene,
我在想"天啊  她演技真棒"
I'm thinking, "Boy, she is a great actress."
但我也在想"她太性感了"
But I'm also thinking, "She is hot."
你觉得我性感
You think I'm hot?
你拥有这个房间
You own the room.
或许我们应该
We should probably get the...
对  我们应该
Oh, yeah. Yeah, we should get...
当洁西卡接吻时
So when Jessica kisses a man...
她通常会把
...she usually puts...
双手放在那个男人脸上
...both her hands on the man's face.
我注意到了  那是因为她很热情吗
I notice that. Is that because she's so passionate?
不  那样摄影机才能只拍到她
No, it's because that way the camera only sees her.
你想试试看吗
You want to try it?
好的
Yeah, okay.
太棒了  真的很不错
That was good. That was really good.
但我想你手的位置不对
But I think that maybe your hands
它们应该
are just a little off. They should be right...
我想吃点点心
Well, I feel like a snack.
你要吃点脆饼吗 它是你故乡苏格兰的点心
Do you want some shortbread? It's Scottish, like you are.
谢谢  但所有有关苏格兰的东西我都不爱
Oh, no, thanks. I don't like anything from my Scottish heritage.
什么
What?
就是因为 我全家都被逐出了英格兰
Well, it's just that my entire family was run out of Scotland by...
是维京人干的
...Vikings.
听上去像是
It sounds to me like
你的家族已经做好准备重溯苏格兰之根了
you family's ready to rediscover its Scottish roots.
你不能在婚礼上吹风笛
You can't play bagpipes at the wedding!
你们怎么知道
How did you know about that?
我们在家都听到你吹了
We heard you play from your apartment.
是你们去报警的
Were you the ones who called the cops?
那不重要
That's not really important right now.
重要的是  我们谢谢你的好意
What is important is, while we appreciate the gesture...
我们只是觉得我们的婚礼
...we just don't feel that
和风笛不搭调
bagpipes are appropriate for our wedding.
-为什么  -因为我们讨厌风笛
- Why not? - Because we hate them.
给我个机会给你们表演
Just give me a chance to perform for you,
然后你们再决定
then decide whatever you want.
我也不会告诉你们我要吹哪首曲子
I'm not gonna tell you what song I'm gonna play either.
只不过在曲子结束之后
Let's just say when it's over...
我们肯定会小小庆祝一番
...l'll bet there'll be a wee bit of celebration.
嘿
Hey, hey!
是谁
Who is it?
我是汤姆  我来拿手机的
It's Tom. I'm here to pick up the phone.
为什么要由你去开门
Why do you get to answer the door?
-为什么不行  -因为这里是我家
- Why shouldn't I ? - Because it's my apartment.
那么由我来把手机交给他
Then I get to give him the cell phone.
希望你能好好跟他解释那些打到中国的电话
Okay. Good luck explaining all the calls to China.
嗨
Hi.
我们争执了多久
Wow, how long were we arguing for?
你不是那个忘了拿手机的人
You're not the man who left the phone.
-对  他是我的助理  -他会来吗
- No, that's my assistant. - Is he coming?
不
No.
-你能让我们谈一下吗  -没问题
- Could you give us one second? - Sure.
我们马上回来  先生
We'll be right back, sir.
-我们该怎么办  -我不知道
- What do we do? - I don't know.
你能相信吗
Can you believe this?
我们在等一个帅哥
We were waiting for a hot guy,
结果来了一个超级大帅哥
and then an even hotter one shows up.
我知道
I know.
什么
What?
瑞秋  听我说
Rachel, listen...
如果你能把他让给我  我真的欠你一个大人情
...if you let me have him, then I will really owe you one.
好
All right.
好吧  我把他让给你
All right, I will let you have him.
但你欠我一个大人情
But you owe me. You owe me big.
哪一位漂亮的小姐要陪我去吃晚餐
Which one of you lovely ladies am I taking to dinner?
是我
Oh, that'd be me, sir.
-你先请  -谢谢
- After you. - Oh, thank you.
太棒了
Nice.
你的确坐拥那房间
Well, you certainly own that room.
事实上整间公寓都是我租的
Actually, I rent the whole place.
我明白你的意思了  谢谢夸奖
I just got what you meant. Thank you.
-嗨  -嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
天
Oh, my God.
杰西卡·罗卡哈德在我的公寓里
Oh, Jessica Lockhart! in my apartment!
我是你的头号大影迷  头号大影迷
I am such a huge fan. I am such a huge fan.
很高兴能见到
It's nice to know...
莫妮卡
Monica!
她是我的室友瑞秋
That's my roommate, Rachel.
难怪你家会有女人内衣
That explains all the womers underwear.
是啊
Sure.
我的天啊  是真的
Oh, my God, it's true!
天啊  我能请你帮我一个忙吗
Can I just ask you to do me just one favor?
当然可以
Certainly.
你能打我一巴掌吗
Would you slap me right here in the face?
我很乐意
I'd love to,
但我的律师说  我不能再那么做了
but my lawyer said I can't do that anymore.
好  走吧
All right, here we go.
等一下  还有一件事
No, wait. Just one more thing.
-你个愚蠢的贱人  -我真的不能打你
- You're a stupid bitch. - I really can't slap you.
-天啊  你太棒了  -谢谢你们过来
- My God, you're great. - Thanks for stopping by.
-我真的很抱歉  -不
- I am so sorry about that. - Oh, no.
我习惯被人崇拜了  别担心
Being adored, I'm used to it. Don't worry about it.
-天  -怎么了
- Oh, my God. - What?
他们寄了今天的剧本给我
They sent me today's script.
他们从来没有给我寄过剧本
They never send me the script.
-是吗  -我一直都昏迷不醒
- They don't? - I'm just in a coma.
这代表我有台词了
This must mean I have lines.
我是怎么死的
How does it happen?
你摔下马  然后撞到电篱笆
You get thrown from a horse into an electric fence.
什么  洁西卡讨厌马
A what? Jessica hates horses.
经过这件事  她也不会喜欢电
After this, she's not gonna be crazy about electricity either.
在妈妈的马鞍上动手脚是个好点子  弗莱德克
Loosening the saddle on Mother's horse was brilliant, Fredrick.
电篱笆那个点子太妙了
And the electric fence, inspired.
谢谢你  亲爱的
Thank you, sweetheart.
我不敢相信她真的死了
I can't believe she's really gone.
看看你的四周  一切都是我们的
Look around you. All of this is ours.
我可不那么认为
I don't think so.
你是谁
Who are you?
怎么了  笛娜
What's the matter, Dina?
你不认得你自己的
Don't you recognize your own...
妈妈吗
...mother?
卡  大家都演得很好  谢谢
Cut! That was great, everybody. Thank you.
那真的是太棒了
That was so wonderful!
我想你比我更适合演洁西卡
I think that you're a better Jessica than I ever was.
-不  -当然不是  但你真的很棒
- Oh, no. - Of course not, but you were good.
谢谢
Thanks.
好消息  我找到新工作了
Good news. I got another job.
太棒了  是什么样的工作
Great. Hey, all right! What is it?
我要到瓜达拉哈拉拍电影
A film in Guadalajara.
机场
The airport?
不  那是拉瓜迪亚机场
No, that's LaGuardia.
-我要去墨西哥  -哇
- This is Mexico. - Oh, wow.
你会去多久
Well, how long will you be gone?
八个月
Eight months.
那真的很久
That's a really long time.
对  但你可以来看我
Yeah, but you could come and visit me.
我敢说你能在那里也能拥有几个地方
I bet that you could own a few places down there.
或许我该先在纽约买房子
Oh, you know, I should probably buy a place in the city first.
我又刚刚才领会到你的意思  那还真是
And I just got what you meant. That is...
-很容易理解错  -是很容易理解错
- That's a tricky one. - It's tricky.
好运
Good luck.
你也是
You too.
请记住
Now, remember...
我还在学习当中
...l'm still learning.
一  二  三  四
One, two, three, four!
你们都知道这首歌  一起唱吧
You know the song. Sing along.
怎么样
So?
-不  -不
- No. - No.